So friends, in today's video we will talk about
ICC Lombard. Basically, the
company has disclosed its quarterly numbers,
so let's see
what is there in the quarterly numbers,
but before that, let me tell you that the company has
also announced to give dividend at the rate of 5.5% today as the final dividend,
so remember, the
company is going to give dividend at the rate of 5.5%. The
record date for this is that the company has told that it is going to
keep another annual meeting in which it will
tell when the company is going to fix the record date.
Let's see the numbers of that company
because the numbers are looking very
impressive. Let's see how they are
because it is number one in the insurance sector, so there is a lot of
hope too. Let's
see from this number, how the numbers are given. The numbers are
given in the link for the database. I will
explain to you by converting them into cross.
Talking about the previous quantity, if we
look at the total income of the company in the last quarter, then it is
around 4362 crores.
Whenever you look at it, it is around 4636 crores last year, but then it is
5255 crores.  It has been around Rs.
100 crore, so if we look at the year-on-year order, then
you have seen a great growth. If we talk about the year, then
indirectly we can say that there is a
growth of around 15% in the revenue of the company.
If we go quarter to quarter, then
you will see an indirect growth of around 20% there. So the
income of the company has been seen to be distributed very well
in this quarter.
Let us see what has happened to the company, so see
what is the previous quantum. In the last quarter, the
company had spent Rs. 85,000 crore, last
year Rs. 3000,626 crore. When this also takes place, then
you can see that the company's revenue is around Rs. 3976 crore, so the
expenses of the company are also seen to be under control to a great extent. Let us see
what the overall profit of the company comes out to be. So, let us
see the
net profit of the company in the last quarter.
If we look at the after-take, then the company was in profit
of Rs. 352 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was Rs. 312 crore,
which till now the
company's profit has been Rs. 436 crore.
You have seen a good growth in the profit of the company as well,
you can say that there is a growth of around 40%,
whereas if we go quarter to quarter, then
you will see a growth of around 22%, so the
numbers of the company are looking very good in this quarter, if we
look at the NPA of the company also, then
you can see a good improvement, so
its earning numbers are good, if we talk about apps, then
you are seeing a good growth there too, it used to be ₹718
in the last quarter, last year it is 6.37
till now, so it is around 8.90, so its
earning numbers are excellent, on top of that the company has
also given a discount of 550, so that can also be seen as a point, that is a
positive factor,
so that's all for today, if you like the video then please
like it and also subscribe to the channel,
thank you